(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
3D SHOWCASE
JULY 28 (FRI)
20:00~ (WIB) / 22:00~ (JST)
#AnyaMelfissa3D
ア・ア・オ・エ・オ・エ・オ・エ・オ
A-a-o-e-o-e-o-e-o
アイウエ
Lyrics ・ Composition: SAKURAmoti / 美波
Arrangement: SAKURAmoti / 真船勝博
Aiu-e
Lyrics ・ Composition: SAKURAmoti / Minami
Arrangement: SAKURAmoti / Katsuhiro Mafune
ねえ その言葉に私にちょっと興味ないの
Hey, aren't you a little interested in those words of mine?
ああ そう じゃあいいか
Ah, I see. Then never mind.
私全部全部わかってたいの
I want to understand everything, every single thing.
ダメなよう？ そんなこと言われても
No good? Even if you say that...
意味わかんないじゃん
...it makes no sense.
五感現象 異常上昇
Sensation phenomenon, abnormal rise.
どこがいいの？なんてよく聞かれるけどさ
"What's so good about it?" They ask me often, but...
わからないでいいよ
It's fine if you don't understand.
愛に溢れて止まらないだけ
I'm just overflowing with love and can't stop.
ア・ア・ア・イ・エ・イ
A-a-a-i-e-i
つまらない どいつもこいつも
It's boring, everyone's the same,
飽きないの？
Don't you get tired?
さあ どうする ダーリン？
Now, what will you do, Darling?
おお もう絶対 僕にアイウエちゃってしょうがない
Ah, geez. You're definitely falling for me, it can't be helped.
いつもの継ぎ足し足しするのは忍びないけど
I feel bad about always just adding more to it, but...
行ったり
Going...
来たり
...and coming back.
泣き枯れちゃっても
If I cry myself dry,
困っちゃうし
I'll be in trouble.
いつまでたったって堪えらんないからさ
Because I can't bear it no matter how much time passes.
僕は今日も逃げるのさ
I'm running away again today.
フラフラ
Wandering around,
危険一髪 あなたは僕の運命の人
A close call. You're the one for me.
許してよ こんなのあんまりじゃーん！
Forgive me. This is just too much!
よそう 決めないで
Stop it. Don't decide,
選べないで
Don't choose.
僕は全部全部を愛していたいの
I want to love everything, every single thing.
最低だよ そんなこと言われても
That's the worst. Even if you say that,
別に十々承知
I'm well aware.
ラブソングに酔い酔い ほどほど
Drunk on love songs, in moderation.
何がダメなの？なんてよく聞かれるけどさ
"What's so bad about it?" They ask me often, but...
他人事もいいところ
It's none of my business.
愛に当たって砕けて立ち上がるだけ
Just hitting love head-on and picking myself back up.
奇想天外 何を言っているのかな？
Bizarre. What are you saying?
悔しであーらら言葉に言っちゃって
Regrettably, the words just come out.
アイノアジ チェリアジ ぜんぶだめね
The taste of love, the taste of cherry. It's all no good.
女の子面倒結構
Girls are such a bother.
百花繚乱 雪吹雪いても 天真爛漫 冷静になれど
Flowers blooming in profusion, even in a blizzard. Innocent and cheerful, even if I become calm.
...ンは等しくお利口なヤツらさ
...are equally clever guys.
銃半信半疑 飛ばして
Half-trusting, half-doubting guns, flying.
ご愛顧 お大事?
Your patronage, take care?
止めどない この愛の
This unstoppable love.
アイウエオ
AIUEO
教えて 息づらして するくたして
Tell me, making it hard to breathe, making it...
知らないって 知らないって
"I don't know," "I don't know."
私もっと全部をわかっていたいの
I want to understand everything more.
ダメだよって そんなこと言われても
Even if I'm told "No, you can't."
意味わかんないじゃん
It doesn't make sense.
承諾事項 意向上昇
Agreed matters, rising intentions.
まったく どうしようもない君に
To you, who are absolutely hopeless.
天前を だらしないくらいがちょうどいい
Being pampered, just a bit slovenly is just right.
愛が溢れて溢れて止まらない
Love overflows and overflows, it won't stop.
バチバチもういい加減にして
Now, enough of this crackling.
アイウエオ
AIUEO
これなんだろう なんて説明しよう
What is this? How should I explain it?
アイウエオ
AIUEO
私だけ見ててよ
Just look at me.
心から 許さない
I won't forgive you from the heart.
一瞬でも 一秒でも 交差していたいたい
Even for a moment, even for a second,
I want our paths to cross.
だから一緒にいて
So stay with me.
Hello! Hi everyone! Halo semuanya!
Hello! Hi everyone! Hello everyone!
皆さんこんばんは！
And welcome to my 3D reveal!
Good evening, everyone!
Woo! Have you guys seen my room?
I sang AIUE, one of my favorite songs, yay!
Tadi lihat kan? Aku udah nyanyi dan dance...
Did you see just now?
I've already sung and danced...
and look at my room! Oh my god guys! Guys!
Ingat nggak kalian pas debut?
Do you remember when I debuted?
Ini dari hobo bisa jadi sekarang guys!
From being a hobo to this, guys!
Bisa di sini!
I can be here!
Kalau aku bisa, kenapa kalian tidak bisa?
If I can do it, why can't you?
Gila, motivational keris.
Crazy, motivational keris.
Oh my god. Okay, look at this.
Oh! Look at this, what is this?
Do you guys know what is this?
Yes, this is a cowboy hat.
Karena aku suka pakai itu, apa sih, cowboy emote.
Because I like to use that, what's it, the cowboy emote.
I like to use, I like to use
the cowboy emote a lot...
and I have a cowboy hat with me now!
And look at my table!
There's a lot of stuff here.
Oh my god and who is this?
Who is this? Apakah ini Toaster-kun?
Who is this? Is this Toaster-kun?
Is this the real comeback of Toaster-kun?
Oh my goodness.
Okay, I'm gonna be making a toast real quick.
Okay. Okay, I'll be going back here after this.
Ah! Gila lihat! Lihat kamarku guys!
Ah! Crazy, look! Look at my room, guys!
Lihat kamarku guys! Whoa! So many weapons!
Look at my room, guys! Whoa! So many weapons!
Because I am an ancient weapon.
This is only befitting of an ancient weapon.
で、ここは?
And, here?
おっと。これ、これ、これ。
Oops. This, this, this.
これ、これはファンシーな...
This, this is fancy...
これはファンシーだね。
This is fancy, isn't it?
ちょっと飲んでみようか。
Shall I try drinking a bit?
うわ! うめえ!
Whoa! Delicious!
Okay, that was, that was delicious.
We getting fancy here. Ooh.
ごちそうさまでした。
Thank you for the drink.
Okay! Apakah toast-ku sudah jadi?
Okay! Is my toast ready?
おれ? Wait what?
Huh? Wait what?
Ha? Ini kenapa?
Huh? What's happening?
Woi woi woi woi!
Lagi 3D reveal jangan nge-bug woi!
It's a 3D reveal, don't bug out woi!
Aku tahu aku bug-tester tapi jangan...
I know I'm a bug tester, but don't...
Waah!
Woi tunggu! Tunggu bentar!
Woi wait! Wait a second!
Bug-nya nanti! Bug-nya nanti!
Bug later! Bug later!
Jangan sekarang!
Ini lagi 3D reveal, kocak!
Not now!
This is a 3D reveal, you've got to be kidding!
Oh my god! Don't bug on me! It's my 3D reveal.
Oh! Oh my god! Okay.
Aduh pengen...
Aduuh, I just want...
I just wanted to eat one toast.
And this is what I have to go through.
I know I'm a bug tester, but not like this, man.
Oh my god, let's put my hat first.
Let's put my hat back.
Okay. Alright, okay, let's eat this one toast.
ああ、おいしい!
Ah, delicious!
This is so good guys.
As expected from Toaster-kun.
Thank you so much Toaster-kun.
あ、おいしいこれ。ありがて。
Ah, this is delicious. Thankful.
ありがとうな、トースターくん。お?
Thanks, Toaster-kun. Oh?
What? Who's that?
Siapa? Siapa? Siapa?
Who? Who? Who?
Ada, ada call dari PC, siapa?
There's, there's a call from the PC, who?
Siapa itu? Who's that?
Who's that? Who's that?
Hello? Halo? Moshi-moshi?
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hello? Halo?
Hello? Hello?
Halo!
Hello!
Siapa tu?
Who's that?
Ha-lo!
Hello!
Haheng! Perkenalkan dirimu Haheng, siapa?
Haheng! Introduce yourself, Haheng, who?
Omedetou! 3D omedetou!
Congratulations! Congratulations on your 3D!
Arigatou!
Thank you!
Siapa namamu?
What is your name?
Aku Ayunda Risu Hololive ID Gen 1!
I'm Ayunda Risu from Hololive ID Gen 1!
Wadeeeh keren! Dan di sebelahnya ada Jamet eh bukan siapa siapa namamu bukan Jamet kan?
Whoa, cool! And next to her is Jamet... wait, no. What's your name? It's not Jamet, right?
Jamet Jamet... Aku Omet... gak...
Jamet, Jamet... I'm Omet... no...
Aku Omet Kaelia Omet.
I'm Omet, Kaelia Omet.
Omet dua orang. Omet dua orang ya.
Omet for two. Omet for two, okay.
Omet dua orang, okay. ID Gen 3!
Omet for two, okay. ID Gen 3!
Widiih, Risu-senpai and Kaelia, thank you so much for coming!
Whoa, Risu-senpai and Kaelia, thank you so much for coming!
How do you guys like my room? Bagaimana kamarku guys?
How do you guys like my room? How is my room, guys?
Wih gila keren banget! Keren banget kan ya.
Whoa, this is crazy cool! It's really cool, right?
Gila banget gak sih? Lihat deh di meja itu.
Isn't it crazy? Look at that table.
Mau apa? Mau looting.
What for? I want to loot.
Mau looting... jangan looting aku.
I want to loot... don't loot me.
Jangan looting aku, aku dari hobo bisa berusaha sekeras ini...
Don't loot me. I worked so hard from being a hobo...
...untuk dapetin kamar yang sekeren ini. Gila.
...to get a room as cool as this. It's crazy.
Bagi-bagilah... bagi-bagilah.
Share some... share some.
Liat deh guys di meja ini aku lumayan banyak senjata ya guys.
Look guys, on this table I have quite a lot of weapons.
Aku lumayan banyak ituin senjata... aduh pokoknya ada banyak deh.
I've gathered quite a few weapons... anyway, there are many.
Di situ ada... ada gun... dan ada keris. Oh my god!
Over there is... a gun... and a keris. Oh my god!
Just like me for real for real.
Oh my god, but I have something even more cooler.
Oh my god, but I have something even cooler.
Aku ada yang lebih keren guys.
I have something even cooler, guys.
Wih apa itu? Apa tuh?
Whoa, what is it? What is it?
Okay... Jyan!
Okay... Ta-da!
Widiih! Apa ini Pai-sen? Ini apa tuh Pai-sen?
Whoa! What's this, Pai-sen? What is this, Pai-sen?
Itu... itu adalah Dagger Sakti!
That... that is a Magic Dagger!
Yes! Wow... Dagger Sakti.
Yes! Wow... Magic Dagger.
Wih gila keren keren... keren keren keren.
Whoa, crazy cool... cool cool cool.
Kalau gitu nih kalau gitu nih sekalian ya sekalian.
In that case, in that case, while we're at it.
Apa?
What?
Karena sudah ada dagger yang sangat keren...
Since you have such a cool dagger...
...aku mau request pose boleh ya?
...can I request a pose?
Oh boleh dong! Let's go! Asik.
Of course! Let's go! Awesome.
Kalau gitu ya langsung aja nih aku tuh dapat image gitu...
Then let's get right to it. I have this image...
...kalau Anya itu berpose kayak ini...
...of Anya posing like this...
...kayak sebelum fighting gitu, kayak idle pose gitu.
...like before a fight, like an idle pose.
Kayak di fighting game gitu.
Like in a fighting game.
Oh kayak di fighting game gitu. Betul.
Oh, like in a fighting game. Right.
Okay coba coba... gimana ya posenya?
Okay, let's try... how should the pose be?
Widiih! Oh! Gila! Sangar guys!
Whoa! Oh! Crazy! So fierce, guys!
Mantap! Mantap banget gak sih. Keren banget.
Excellent! It's so good. So cool.
Ada satu lagi by the way. Ada satu lagi guys.
There's one more by the way. There's one more, guys.
Apa nih apa nih? Aku juga mau request.
What is it? I want to request one too.
Oh iya dari Kaelia juga. Apa apa?
Oh right, from Kaelia too. What is it?
Okay bentar aku ambil dulu.
Okay, wait, let me get it first.
Jyan! Apa ini? Widiih!
Ta-da! What's this? Whoa!
Gila gak sih? Keren banget gak sih ini?
Isn't it crazy? Isn't this so cool?
Ini revolver guys. Ini revolver ala Anya ya guys.
This is a revolver, guys. Anya-style revolver, guys.
Widiih... mau request apa Kaelia tadi? Katanya mau request.
Whoa... what did Kaelia want to request? You said you had a request.
Boleh boleh. Mau apa?
Sure, sure. What is it?
Kamu tau gak kayak yang di cover-cover film gitu...
You know like those movie covers...
...biasanya di movie-movie cover gitu.
...usually on movie covers.
Ya?
Yeah?
Nah jadi kamu hadap belakang dulu.
So, first, face the back.
Hadap belakang? Okay.
Face the back? Okay.
Terus kepalanya menghadap depan, muka muka hadap depan.
Then turn your head to the front, face forward.
Kepalanya balik balik... oh kayaknya aku tau deh apa yang kamu maksud.
Head turned... oh, I think I know what you mean.
Gitu? Iya iya terus tangannya kayak ke atas gitu.
Like this? Yeah, and then your hand is like up there.
Itu bisa buat nembak gak?
Can you shoot with that?
Iya bisa buat nembak dong. Mau lihat nih?
Yeah, of course I can shoot. Want to see?
Coba dong coba dong.
Show us, show us.
Wih! Widiih! Oh! Widiih!
Whoa! Whoa! Oh! Whoa!
Gini kan yang menurut kamu?
Is this what you meant?
Iya iya coba posenya... widiih! Gila!
Yeah, yeah, keep the pose... whoa! Crazy!
Okay gimana guys keren banget. Thank you banget guys.
Okay, how was that guys? So cool. Thank you so much, guys.
Keris satu ini guys, gila keren banget.
This one keris, guys, it's crazy cool.
Makasih banyak lho guys sudah datang.
Thank you so much for coming, guys.
Makasih! Thank you Anya! Thank you-nya Anya!
Thanks! Thank you Anya! Thank you, Anya!
Thank you-nya Anya! Good, thank you lho!
Thank you, Anya! Good, thank you!
Bye bye! Bye bye! Arigato!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Thank you!
Hai, jadi itu ya guys Risu-senpai dan Jamet eh bukan Kaelia.
So that was Risu-senpai and Jamet... wait, no, Kaelia.
Thank you so much to Risu-senpai and Kaelia for coming...
...to my 3D Showcase. Apakah kita ada guest lagi?
...to my 3D Showcase. Do we have any more guests?
Do we have any more guests I wonder?
Oh! Kita kita kita... oh!
Oh! They're here, they're here... oh!
Are? Mana ini? Mana ini?
Huh? Where are they? Where are they?
Lah, ngebak guys. Kok ngebak guys?
Wait, it's bugged, guys. Why is it bugged?
Anya! Miko dayo! Kitasoyo!
Anya! It's Miko! I'm here!
Sono koe wa... Miko-senpai! Kitan da yo!
That voice... Miko-senpai! You're here!
Sono koe wa... Miko-senpai nyaharo!
That voice... Miko-senpai, nyahallo!
Anya haro! Miko senpai nyaharo!
Anya-hallo! Miko-senpai, nyahallo!
Ah, kimashita kimashita.
Ah, she's here. She's finally here.
Ya kite kurete arigato gozaimasu!
Thank you so much for coming!
Hai, ja jiko shoukai.
Okay, please introduce yourself.
えーっと、にゃっはろー！
Er, nyahallo!
ホロライブ…じゃ、ジャパンJPのエリート巫女 さくらみこです！
Hololive... Ja-, Japan JP's Elite Miko, Sakura Miko!
エリート巫女 さくらみこです、よろしくお願いします！
Elite Miko Sakura Miko here, please take care of me!
EN?
ホロライブEN?
Hololive EN?
No, no, no.
No?
Not EN.
あなたJPですか?
Are you JP?
いや、IDです。インドネシア。
No, I'm ID. Indonesia.
インドネシア。
Indonesia.
日本語うま...
Your Japanese is so good...
日本語うますぎるなちょっと。
Your Japanese is way too good.
みこより上手いんじゃないのちょっとこれ。
It might even be better than Miko's.
いやいやいやいや、そんな。
No, no, no, not at all.
いやー、あーにゃ小さいねー、おめでとー。
Anya, you're so small! Congrats!
いやそんな変わらんやろ、そんな変わらんやろ。
We're not that different! We're not!
変わるよ!みこお姉さんだもんね。
We are! Miko is the big sister after all.
いやいやいやいや、お姉さんなのこれ?
No way, you're the big sister?
かわいい〜。
So cute.
え、なんでみこのこと呼んでくれたの?
So, why did you invite Miko today?
え、やっぱここ最近めちゃくちゃ仲いいじゃないですか、我々。
Well, we've been getting along so well lately, haven't we?
まあ、デートもしたしね。
Well, we did go on a date.
ね、デートもしたしね。
Right, we did.
ぬいぐるみも2つくれたもんね。
You even gave me two plushies.
ね、取ってくれたもんね、UFOキャッチャーで。
Yeah, you won them for me at the crane game.
めっちゃ嬉しそうだった。もう。
You looked so happy.
肉まん、あんなでっかいやつで、肉まんもくれたんだよ。
And you gave me that huge meat bun too.
ね、優しいよね。
Yeah, you're so kind.
やったぜ、いや、照れるな。
I did it! Man, I'm blushing.
いや、でも我々もね、色んな繋がりがありますから、ヘリとか。
But we have various connections, like helicopters.
あ、そうだ!
Oh, that's right!
ジャンプした時とか。ヘリ、こうシュルーンってやつ。
Like when we jumped. The heli going 'vroom'.
ありましたね、シュルーンってやつ。ボカーンってやつね。
Right, that 'vroom' one. And the 'kaboom' one.
ボカーンってやつね。
The 'kaboom' one.
はい、ということで。
Yes, and so...
まあ、私ね、あの3Dお披露目で、やはり絵を描きたいんですよ。
Well, for my 3D showcase, I really want to draw.
絵を描きたい?
You want to draw?
そう、絵を描きたくて。
Yes, I want to draw.
え、みこも描くー。
Eh, Miko wants to draw too!
お、でも普通に絵を描くのがね、ちょっとつまんないんじゃないですか。
But just drawing normally is a bit boring, isn't it?
ということで対決、対決したいと思って。
So I thought we should have a battle.
いいんですか? みこと。
Is that okay? With Miko?
みこ先輩、そう、噂によるとね、絵が上手いので。
Miko-senpai, yeah, I heard rumors you're good at drawing.
まあそれはまあ確かに、JPの中では中の下ぐらいの...
Well, certainly, among JP members, I'm around lower-middle...
まあ上手いよね、エリートだから。何でもできるし。
Well, I'm good. I'm an elite, I can do anything.
じゃあこの後見るか? うん、みこのやつ。
Wanna see it later then? My drawing.
そう、でも、まだね、あの、まだまだゲストがいます。
Right, but there are still more guests.
え、ゲスト!?
What, guests!?
ゲスト、この2人!
Guests, these two!
Hi! Hello!
Hi hi! Hello!
Introduce yourselves, starting from Mumei.
Yes, yes, hello, ohai! I'm Nanashi Mumei.
I'm a member of Hololive English -Council-...
...and the 'Brown hair, don't care' gang! Yoroshiku!
...and the 'Brown hair, don't care' gang! Nice to meet you!
Brown hair, don't care! Welcome!
And Zeta!
Hello, I'm Zeta from Hololive ID Gen 3! Yay!
Yay! So cute!
でね、この後、まあイラスト、まあ絵の対決やるんですけど。
So, after this, we're doing a drawing battle.
まあね、あの、スタッフさんからね、あの、お題ね、あの、もらったんですよ。
Well, you see, I got a prompt from the staff.
あー、いいじゃないですか、そのお題。
Oh, that sounds good, that prompt.
で、そのお題を描いて、で、ムメイとゼタと対決でございます。
So we'll draw that prompt and battle with Mumei and Zeta.
みこたちが描いて、それを当てるってことね。
So we draw it and they have to guess it.
そう、あーなるほどなるほど。
Right, I see, I see.
So what we will be doing is that staff thought of a prompt...
...and me and Miko-senpai have to draw them...
...and Mumei and Zeta will be the ones guessing what prompt is it.
Okay! Yay! Let's go!
We have one minute to draw. 1分。1分ね。
We have one minute to draw. One minute. One minute.
1分で。60秒。OK。描きましょ。
In one minute. 60 seconds. Okay. Let's draw.
忙しいね。
That's busy.
1分で描きましょ。
Let's draw in one minute.
これを使います。
We'll use these.
ドン、ドン。
Bam, bam.
Whoa! Canvases!
本格的ですね、アーニャさん。
This is very professional, Anya-san.
ね、これはいいですよ。
Right? This is good.
ここで座らせていただいて。よいしょっと。
Let's take a seat here. There we go.
とりあえず、Mumei and Zeta, close your eyes, because we will be showing the prompt.
Anyway, Mumei and Zeta, close your eyes, because we will be showing the prompt.
見ないでね。見ないで。
Don't look. Don't look.
Close your eyes... 見ててね。
Close your eyes... Watch, okay?
何のお題かなー。
I wonder what the prompt is.
あひるに告白するスバル
Subaru confessing to a duck
あ!
Oh!
あー、なるほどですね。
Ah, I see.
あー、OK OK OK。
Ah, OK OK OK.
Can we take a peak?
OK OK OK OK。
OK OK OK OK.
でも1分なんだよな。
But it's only one minute.
1分だね。どうなるんかな。
One minute, huh. I wonder how it'll go.
Okay, open your eyes, if you haven't.
Okay! My eyes are open!
よし、じゃあ、始めますか。
Alright, then, shall we start?
行きますか。
Shall we go?
Ready?
Ready!
Set... Go!
Okay! Okay!
始まりました。
It has begun.
ここで今まで培ったものを全て...
I'll use everything I've cultivated until now...
Do you think one minute is enough to draw anything?
No.
They will prevail.
え、どうやって描くんだったっけ?
Wait, how was I supposed to draw this?
ちょっ...
Wait...
They have so much passion in their eyes.
みこはもう余裕ですけど、ちなみに。
I'm quite confident, by the way.
お?
Oh?
We should be able to do this, Zeta.
Exactly. We should be able to figure this out.
Can you? We can maybe figure it out based on their hand movements.
待って、手の動き?
Wait, hand movements?
I think I know what it is.
You know what it is?
I definitely know what it is based just on their movement.
Okay, um...
...it could be, I don't know, something related to their emotions maybe? I'm not too sure.
せめて...
At least...
これだけは伝わってほしい。
...I hope at least this gets through.
Oh, what do you think?
これだけは...
At least this...
伝わって。
...get through.
これだけは伝わってほしい。
I hope at least this gets through.
I guess you're right. It could be a variety of things.
ちょ... 待って。
Wai... Wait.
ちょっと難しかった、これ。
This was a bit difficult.
いや、これは...
No, this is...
絵心だからね、あにゃ、これは。
It's about artistic spirit, Anya.
そうだね、絵心が伝わるかどうかだから。
Right, it's about whether the artistic spirit gets through.
せめて、あの...
At least, um...
まあ、誰かだけに伝わってほしいな。
Well, I hope at least one person gets it.
そうね。
Right.
OK, OK.
誰か一人は100%。
Someone will get it 100%.
Let's show the show!
うん。
Yeah.
OK?
OK.
OK, let's see Anya's!
Yes!
ドン！
Ta-da!
せめて誰かだけに伝わってほしい、これは。
I hope at least someone gets this.
もうなんなのよ、これ。
What even is this?
That's it?
Is that a duck? I was about to say it's a duck.
Mumei, what do you think that is? I can't tell.
This is my masterpiece!
It's very obvious!
Who is it, senpais?
OK, let's now see Miko's.
ドン！
Ta-da!
Oh, a platypus!
可愛んじゃねえか。
Isn't that cute.
可愛んじゃねえか、そんなのよりずっと。
Isn't that cute, much more than that one.
いやいやいや、伝わるよ、伝わるよ。
No, no, no, it'll get through, it'll get through.
いやいやいや、No, no, no, mine is better!
No, no, no, mine is better!
Are we doing the same thing? I guess we'll find out.
OK.
何を描いたかってとこが...
What we drew is...
Winner!
Mumei-Zeta discussion time!
What person do you guys think this is?
Mumei can go first.
All right. I think it is Subaru-senpai talking to a platypus.
OK. It does look like a platypus.
I'm gonna say the same thing, except a duck maybe.
Huh huh huh.
シュバシュバ、シュバシュバ、シュバシュバ。
Shuba shuba, shuba shuba, shuba shuba.
果たして？
Really?
Is it wrong? Is it correct?
正解かどうかどうだ？
Is it correct or not?
Is that a platypus?
Your answer?
Final answer?
A platypus, I guess. I'll go with a platypus.
Duck-platypus.
OK.
Yeah, platypus. Platypus is more likely. Let's just go with that.
正解はこちら！
The correct answer is here!
そう、これむずいよな。
Yeah, this is hard.
正解は...
The correct answer is...
ドン！
Ta-da!
正解は...
The correct answer is...
正解かどうかどうだ。
Is it correct or not?
あひるに告白するスバル
Subaru confessing to a duck
Confessing! Confessing to a duck!
Confessing to a duck?
告白するスバル。
Subaru confessing.
みこさん、あひるしか見てなくて...
Miko-san, I was only looking at the duck...
あんま覚えてなくて。
...so I didn't remember well.
あれ挨拶かな？
Was that a greeting?
挨拶？
A greeting?
なんか、私これ告白してるから...
Like, since I'm confessing here...
なんか心がハッピーになっちゃったんだけど。
...my heart just became happy.
あ、そういうことね。
Oh, I see.
Yeah, it's not a platypus!
圧があるよ、このスバルさん。
There's pressure in this Subaru-san.
It's not a platypus!
なんか圧が凄いのよね、私の。
Like, the pressure is amazing in mine.
うん。
Yeah.
ちょっと圧があるな。
It does have some pressure.
Yeah, my Subaru-senpai is definitely confessing to a duck.
That is a duck.
Interesting.
Interesting, interesting.
I know, right?
Well, Mumei...
...which art do you like the best out of these two?
一番好きなのはどれ？
Which one do you like best?
I have to go with Anya's...
...because I just love the expression that you put on Subaru-senpai. It's so cute.
Anya's art is favorite!
やっぱ、やっぱね、絵心がね...
As expected, the artistic spirit...
もう恵まれてるって。
...is truly gifted.
絵心！
Artistic spirit!
恵まれてるって。
Is truly gifted.
みこの方があるでしょ、あれ。
Miko's is more like it, right?
だって、小物使いしてるし、ここ、見てこれ、小物。
Because I used accessories, look here, accessories.
これやってほしいわ、昴先輩に。
I want Subaru-senpai to do this.
Yeah, thank you so much, Mumei.
What about you, Zeta?
OK, for me...
...I would have to go with Miko-senpai.
Look at that beautiful platypus.
でも可愛いよね、これ。
But it's cute, isn't it?
ツンデレじゃね？
It's tsundere, right?
お前のこと好きだ、あ、そうそう。
"I like you," ah, right.
別に、好きなんて... みたいな。
Like, "It's not like I like you..."
そう、別に好きなわけじゃないのよね。
Right, it's not like I like you.
可愛、別に。
Cute, not really.
ツンデレ。
Tsundere.
Yeah, Subaru-senpai is confessing.
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
可愛いよね。
Cute, isn't it?
Oh my god.
I thought it was Subaru-senpai scolding the duck.
You know what? I thought the same thing.
なんか、あひるに怒ってるみたいな、と思った。
I thought it was like she's scolding the duck.
ああ、ちょっとね。
Ah, a little bit.
そういう雰囲気あるよね。
It does have that vibe.
まあ、確かにな。
Well, certainly.
スバちゃん素直じゃないから。
Suba-chan isn't honest with herself.
ああ、なるほどね。
Ah, I see.
今日は恥ずかしがってるんだね。
She's being shy today.
だよね。
Right.
やっぱ可愛いわ。
She's so cute.
So cute, Subaru-senpai.
Thank you so much, Zeta and Mumei, for joining us!
ありがとうございます！おめでとう！
Thank you so much! Congratulations!
ありがとう！3D！
Thank you! 3D!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
あ、みこ先輩も、ありがとう、ありがとうございます。
Ah, Miko-senpai, thank you, thank you so much.
いや、こちらこそ、来させてくださって、ありがとうございます。
No, thank you for having me here.
いやあ、楽しかったね。
Man, that was fun.
え、もう終わり？
Wait, it's over already?
え、じゃあさ、あの…え、うん。
Well, then... uh, yeah.
やっぱそこら辺の武器、ちょっと後で持ち帰ってもいいすか？
Can I actually take some of those weapons home later?
それは…それは、アーニャさん…
That's... about that, Anya...
それは、うー。検討します。
That's... uh, I'll consider it.
みこ先輩のために、まあ、ぬいぐるみあげたんじゃないですか。
I already gave you a plushie, didn't I?
まだ欲しいんですか？
You still want more?
いや、もらったけど…
Well, I did get it, but...
かっこいいよね、あれね！やば！
Those are so cool! Insane!
あ、憧れますよね。
Ah, they're quite alluring.
え、じゃあ、持ってるね。
Well then, I'll be waiting.
オッケー。
Okay.
うん、じゃあ頑張ってね。
Yeah, good luck!
オッケー。ありがとう。
Okay, thank you.
ありがとう。ありがとう。
Thank you. Thank you.
この後も、頑張ります。やったー。
I'll keep doing my best. Yay!
バイバイ！みこ先輩！
Bye-bye! Miko-senpai!
バイバイ！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
いやあ、でも、みこ先輩のイラスト、可愛いよね。
Man... but Miko-senpai's illustration is so cute.
ああ。楽しかったな、もう。
Ah, that was so much fun.
楽しかったね。
It was fun, wasn't it?
まだ、まだね、このお披露目はね、続きます。なんと。
This showcase is still... still going on, believe it or not.
さてさて。
Now then.
Let's see what is next on our schedule.
え、え、何？
Eh, wait, what?
また？またコール？
Another one? Another call?
ハロー？ハロー？誰だ？
Hello? Hello? Who is it?
初めまして。
Nice to meet you.
え、わたくし、声優の鈴木みのりと申します。
I'm voice actress Minori Suzuki.
（驚きの声）
(Gasping in shock)
え、アーニャさんがですね、プロジェクトセカイの…
So, I heard that Anya-san likes...
東雲絵名がお好きということで。
Ena Shinonome from Project Sekai.
え、こちらでご縁がありましてですね、今回ボイスコメントを送らせていただきたいと思います。
Since we have a connection here, I wanted to send a voice comment this time.
まずは何より、3Dお披露目できて、おめでとうございます。
First and foremost, congratulations on your 3D showcase.
確かに、私もね、まだこのコメントを撮っている時は…
To be honest, while I'm recording this message...
アーニャさんの可愛い、あの、イラストだったりとかね、ま、3Dじゃないものを拝見しておりますので。
I've only seen Anya-san's cute illustrations and non-3D forms.
またこう進化してね、3Dのアーニャさんになったら、またどんな可愛さが増えてしまうんだという感じで。
So I'm wondering how much cuter she'll become once she's evolved into 3D Anya-san.
個人的にもワクワクしておりますが。
I'm personally very excited about it.
えー、そうですね。アーニャさんがどんな人なんだろうっていうふうに、いろいろ調べていく中で、もちろんあのYouTubeの方も見させていただきましたが。
As I was researching what kind of person Anya-san is, I of course watched your YouTube videos.
あの、シャマという曲を歌っている動画が私、特に好きで。
I especially like the video where you're singing the song 'SHAMA'.
（激しい驚き）
(Intense shock)
あの、アーニャさんの声、可愛らしいお声とシャマのあのキーもね、独特な綺麗なアーニャさんの裏声も聞けて。
I got to hear Anya-san's lovely voice, and your beautiful head voice in the key of 'SHAMA' was just unique.
なんか、うっとりしちゃうというか。爽やかさと、可愛さと、かっこよさが、こう同時に楽しめちゃうアーニャさんの歌声に、一人感動しておりました。
It was enchanting. I was personally moved by Anya-san's singing voice, which lets me enjoy freshness, cuteness, and coolness all at once.
ね。絵名をお好きと言ってくださっていて、なんかこう演じている身としても、絵名の頑張りが誰かに届いているんだなっていうのを実感できて。
You said you like Ena, and as her voice actress, knowing her hard work is reaching someone makes me feel so proud.
とっても嬉しく思っています。
It makes me very happy.
またぜひどこかで、3Dのアーニャさんとね、お会いできたらいいななんて、お話しできたらいいななんて、こっそり思ってます。
I secretly hope to meet and talk with the 3D Anya-san somewhere in the future.
ぜひこれからも頑張ってください。陰ながら応援しております。絵名のこともよろしくお願いします。
Please continue to do your best. I'll be supporting you. And please keep supporting Ena too.
以上、鈴木みのりでした。
That's all from Minori Suzuki.
これは！これはこの後ガチャ回すしかないんですよ！
This! I have no choice but to roll the gacha after this!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
鈴木みのりさん、ありがとうございます！
Suzuki Minori-san, thank you very much!
メッセージ、嬉しい。
The message... I'm so happy.
嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
え？ありがとうございます。
Eh? Thank you.
Wait, what?
What happened?
What just happened, everyone?
What just happened?
Who's that?
Who was that?
What was that?
Bro, I'm sorry, I'm sorry guys. I'm... I'm winning.
I'm winning too much today.
You guys have to admit that I'm winning so much today.
It's not even funny.
Excuse me?
Who was that? I'm trying to process that.
は？まだある？
Huh? There's more?
ハロー？
Hello?
やめてください、もう心が、心がもうぐちゃぐちゃになってます、わたくし。
Please stop, my heart... my heart is already a mess.
誰だ？
Who is it?
アーニャさん、初めまして。
Anya-san, nice to meet you.
声優の佐倉綾音です。
I'm voice actress Ayane Sakura.
この度は、まず3Dお披露目おめでとうございます。
First of all, congratulations on your 3D showcase.
Holy... holy Yagoo...
Holy Yagoo...
というわけで、どうやら配信などで、私の名前をよく出してくださっていたというお話で。
So, I heard that you've been mentioning my name often in your streams.
本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
配信など聞かせていただいたんですけど、
I've listened to your streams and such,
えぇ、聞いてくれるの？
Eh, you listen to them?
とっても可愛い声で「佐倉綾音さん」とか
with such a cute voice, calling me "Sakura Ayane-san" or
「あやねるさん」とか呼んでいただいていて、
"Ayaneru-san,"
あ、私も明日から
and I thought, "Ah, I'll be able to
お仕事頑張れるなっていうふうに思いました。
work hard from tomorrow too."
わ！私も明日から仕事頑張ろ！
Whoa! I'll work hard from tomorrow too!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
むしろこちらがありがとうございますという気持ちです。はい。
Actually, it's me who should be thanking you. Yes.
そうですね、アーニャさん。私、
So, Anya-san. I really love
ウエクラさんのイラストがとっても好きなのですが、
Uekura-san's illustrations,
そのウエクラさんがママなんですよね。
and Uekura-san is your "mama," right?
My mama is amazing, yes!
すっごい可愛いウエクラさんのイラストに
With a voice just as cute as
全然負けないとっても可愛い声で、
Uekura-san's lovely illustrations,
軽快なトーク、楽しい、
you've got this breezy talk—fun,
可愛いだけじゃない面白いトークをされていて、
not just cute but interesting,
おお、すごく素敵だなと思いました。
and I thought it was just wonderful.
日本語もめちゃくちゃお上手ですよね。
Your Japanese is incredibly good, too.
ていうか、バイリンガルっていうことになるんですか？
Or rather, you're bilingual, right?
すっげーカッコいい！
That's so cool!
私も二ヶ国語とか三ヶ国語とか喋りたくなったな。
It makes me want to speak two or three languages.
あー！その通りでございます。
Ah! That is correct.
多分、私よりアーニャさんの方が日本語で喋るの上手だと思います。
I think you're actually better at Japanese than I am.
いやいやいや、さすがに！
No way, that's going too far!
本当に、それぐらい思うほど
Seriously, I've been listening to
字幕とか全然なしにスムーズに配信を聞かせていただいて、
your streams smoothly without any subtitles,
とても楽しませていただきました。
and I've really enjoyed them.
あと一つ気になったのが、
One more thing I was curious about:
アーニャさんのホロライブの紹介ページ、あるじゃないですか。
your Hololive profile page.
そこの紹介欄に、
In the introduction section there,
「基本的に無感情で人間には特に興味がないです。」
"Basically emotionless and not particularly interested in humans."
「見た目で判断しないでください。」
"Please don't judge by appearances."
「愚かな人間どもはいつも見た目で判断しますよね。」って書いてあるんです。
"Foolish humans always judge by appearances, don't they?" is what it says.
これ、あはは、黒歴史っぽい...！
This, ahaha, sounds like a dark past...!
これは、私には興味持っていただいたんですよね。
So... you were interested in me, right?
え！もちろん！
Eh! Of course!
私が人間扱いされてないっていうことではないんですよね。
Wait, does that mean I'm not treated as a human?
いや女神ですよ、佐倉綾音さんは。
No, Sakura Ayane-san is a goddess.
ちょっとこれに関しては、アーニャさんの心を
In that regard, if I've been able to
もし少しでも開かせることができているんだったら、
open Anya-san's heart even a little,
とっても嬉しい、ありがたいことだなと思いながら読んでいました。
I read that thinking how happy and grateful I am.
人間っていいものです。
Humans are good things.
もう知ってるか。
But you probably know that.
多分、素敵な仲間とかリスナーさんに囲まれて知ってると思うんですけど。
Surrounded by wonderful friends and listeners.
これからもぜひ引き続き人間のことをよろしくお願いします。
Please continue to be kind to humans from now on.
何の話だ。というわけで、アーニャさん、改めて本当に3Dお披露目おめでとうございます！
What am I talking about? Anyway, Anya-san, congratulations on your 3D debut!
次はいつかはお喋りできる
Next time, if there's ever
タイミングが来たらその時を楽しみにしています。
a chance for us to talk, I'm looking forward to it.
というわけで、佐倉綾音でした。バイバイ！
Anyway, this was Sakura Ayane. Bye-bye!
それ私ですね、多分死にます。
That's me, I'll probably die.
もう何百年も生きてるんですけど、多分一瞬で死にますね。
I've lived for hundreds of years, but I'll probably die in an instant.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
終わっちゃった... 終わっちゃった。
It's over... It's over.
Was that? Of every dream. Was that?
Guys!
Waduh, aku, aku, aku sudah...
Whoa, I, I, I'm already...
kepalaku sudah tidak bisa, tidak bisa berpikir ya guys, habis itu.
my head already can't, can't think anymore guys, after that.
Thank you so much! Thank you so much to Sakura Ayane-san and Suzuki Minori-san!
鈴木みのりさんも佐倉綾音さんもありがとうございます。
Suzuki Minori-san, Sakura Ayane-san, thank you very much.
もうマジで私の中で熱い声優さんのお二人でございます。
They are truly two voice actresses that I'm really passionate about.
本当にありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます！
Thank you so very much. Thank you. Thank you!
まあということでね、あのお披露目は私の頭もぐちゃぐちゃになったんですけど、
So, this showcase has made my head all scrambled, but
まだ終わってません。終わってないです。
it's not over yet. It's not over.
まだまだあります！
There's still more!
After this, there's still a few more stuffs to show you guys.
Okay, let's go to the next live segment! See you there!
じゃあこの後のライブパートに移るから移動します。
Now, I'm moving on to the live part that's coming up next.
待っててください。
Please wait for it.
Sudah jam berapa ini?
Wait, what time is it?
Aku terlambat untuk pergi kerja lagi.
I've been running late to work again.
Ya biarin deh.
Well, whatever.
アーニャ？アーニャ・メルフィッサ？
Anya? Anya Melfissa?
Lagi di dalam kan?
I know you're inside.
おい、アーニャ！
Hey, Anya!
大家さん？
The landlady?
Ada apa ya?
What's up, I wonder?
はーい？
Yeees?
アーニャ...
Anya...
Kamu tahu hari ini tanggal berapa?
Do you know what date today is already?
Bayar kos woi!
Pay your damn rent!
Wah, akhir-akhir ini aku sering skip kerja juga.
Ugh, I've been skipping work lately, too.
Em, boleh minta simpati?
Err, can I get some pity here?
Jangan- jangan nggak, kayak misalnya, saya bayar bulan depan gitu. Apakah boleh?
Wait, no, like, for example, I can pay next month. Is that okay?
Gak boleh dasar freeloader! Sudah berbulan-bulan kau belum bayar ya! Kalau masih gak bisa bayar juga hari ini, maka pergi sekarang juga dari sini!
No way, you freeloader! You haven't paid for months! If you still can't pay today, then get out of here right now!
Aaaaaaaaaaa! Bentar Ibu, bentar!
AAAAAAAAAA! Wait, ma'am, wait!
Ternyata jadi manusia susah juga ya.
Being human is harder than I thought.
Harus kerja dan melakukan beberapa hal lain hanya untuk bisa makan dan tinggal di tempat yang enak.
You have to work and do many other things just to eat and live in a nice place.
Mungkin menjadi manusia memang bukan ide yang bagus.
Maybe becoming human wasn't such a good idea after all.
Sangat susah beradaptasi.
It's so hard to adapt.
Padahal aku adalah senjata legendaris dari masa lalu.
And yet, I'm a legendary weapon from the past.
Kenapa aku harus melakukan semua hal merepotkan ini?
Why do I have to do all these troublesome things?
Hah... aku capek hari ini.
*Sigh*... I'm tired today.
Tidur di bangku di sini dulu deh.
I'll just sleep on this bench for now.
Good night.
Halo. Akhirnya kamu terbangun.
Hello. You're finally awake.
Apa? Ini di mana? Anda siapa?
What? Where is this? Who are you?
Kamu pingsan di depan studio kami.
You passed out in front of our studio.
Kenalkan, nama saya Mr. Yagoo.
Nice to meet you. I'm Mr. Yagoo.
Silakan minum minuman hangat ini dulu.
Please, have some of this warm drink.
Mr. Yagoo...? Mr. Yagoo...?
ちょっと怪しいんだけど…
(Okay, this is VERY suspicious.)
Ya sudahlah. Salam kenal juga.
Whatever. Nice to meet you too.
Mungkin tidak terlihat dari penampilan, tapi saya merupakan senjata kuno yang legendaris.
I might not look like it, but I'm actually a legendary ancient weapon.
Yah, walaupun baru diusir dari tempat kos saya.
Well, although I was just kicked out of my boarding house.
Makanya! Itu dia!
That's why! Exactly!
Kenapa sih manusia itu begitu kejam?
Why are humans so cruel?
Mana egois pula... saya sungguh tidak paham!
And so selfish... I really don't understand!
Anak muda zaman sekarang tuh begini semua ya?
Is this how all young people are these days?
Terdengar berat sekali.
That sounds rough.
Benar kan!
Right?!
Saya tidak tahu harus bagaimana sekarang.
I really don't know what to do anymore.
Bagaimana jika anda menjadi talent dari agensi kami?
Well... how about becoming a talent for our agency?
Menjadi seorang idol!
As an idol!
Eh? Apa maksudnya?
Eh? What do you mean?
Talent... maksudnya jadi idola VTuber?
Talent... you mean like an idol VTuber?
Eh? Seperti Tokino Sora, idola VTuber terkenal itu?
Eh? Like Tokino Sora, that famous idol VTuber?
Benar. Dia juga bagian dari kami, hololive production.
That's right. She's also part of our hololive production.
Sebagai gantinya, kamu bisa tinggal di sini sementara waktu.
In exchange, you can stay here for the time being.
Aku mau! Mau, mau!
Count me in!
この生活の 虜になっちゃうよ Lady
I'll become a prisoner of this life, Lady.
光を失った おさがりの宝石を 永久に纏って
Forever wearing second-hand jewels that have lost their light.
トリコロージュ / Lyrics + Composition: 煮ル果実
Tricologe / Lyrics + Composition: Nilfruits
救われたの光 救いが虚無になるなんて
The light that saved me became a void,
まるでフィクション トラパネーション 浮き足気分になってんだ
Just like fiction, trepanation, I'm feeling restless.
足枷と鎖に縛られて たった一度の光で会うため
Bound by shackles and chains, just to meet with that one-time light,
この部屋でずっと待ってる 何かを待つ囚人
Waiting in this room forever, a prisoner waiting for something.
出されたものは満遍なく 残さず平らげて
Eating everything that was served without leaving anything behind,
異端な死よりも 誰よりも無個性だった
Being more personality-less than anyone else, even more than a heretical death.
住めば都 暗い歌を何度も何度も吐き捨てて
Any place is home, spitting out dark songs over and over again,
挙句の果て ふれる行為自体が苦手になった
In the end, I became bad at the act of touching itself.
夜中 ふとに映った 煌めく仮面舞踏会
In the middle of the night, a sparkling masquerade ball suddenly reflected.
馬鹿らしいほどに 狂おしいほどに 年甲斐もなく惹き込まれたら
If I'm drawn in so ridiculously, so maddeningly, regardless of my age.
この生活の 虜になっちゃうよ Lady
I'll become a prisoner of this life, Lady.
よく似合ってるってさ お誂え向きだってさ その後のことは見向きもしないくせに
You say it suits me well, you say it's just right, even though you won't even look at what happens after.
生活の 虜になっちゃうよ Lady Lady
A prisoner of life, Lady Lady.
痛みだってさ 言えぬ傷だってさ すべて生き抜いた証
Even pain, even wounds that can't be spoken of, are all proof of having survived.
乗り越える試練 他愛もないことでしょう
A trial to overcome, it's nothing significant, is it?
少し欠けてるピンコパール 迷子になったアイオライト
A slightly chipped pink opal, a lost iolite,
埃を被るトパーズ 孤独なアメトリンもみんな
A dusty topaz, and lonely ametrine, everyone.
それぞれ着飾って 濁って重くなって
Dressing up in their own ways, getting muddy and heavy,
奈落の底 牢獄に 沈んでいくとしても
Even if they sink into the bottom of the abyss, into a prison.
訪れた幸せかぼちゃ 祝祭日みたいに
Like the happiness that arrived, like a public holiday,
すでに決められた予定調和
A pre-established harmony that's already been decided.
...思い出させてしまう
...it makes me remember.
貶めても構わないよと
Go ahead and humiliate me.
希望有りの絶望に変えて依存 依存
Turning hopeful despair into addiction, addiction.
生活の 虜になっちゃうレイデー
Captivated by this life, Lady.
「いつか報われる」
It'll pay off someday."
「認めてもらえる」
I'll be recognized."
気休めの呪文で踊るのさ
Dancing to a hollow spell.
エゴを騙すの
Deceiving the ego.
生活の 終わりはすぐそこレイデー レイデー
The end of this life is right there, Lady, Lady.
綻びを目で追うふりをして
Pretending to eye the frayed edges.
生きていくため 乗り越える試練
An ordeal to overcome just to survive.
仕方ないことでしょう
It can't be helped, can it?
この生活の 虜になっちゃうレイデー
Captivated by this life, Lady.
当たり障りのない大衆的な宝石は
Harmless, common jewels...
もう必要はない濁りさえも綺麗
...are no longer needed; even the blur is beautiful.
生活の 虜になっちゃえレイデー レイデー
Become a captive of this life, Lady, Lady.
生臭かった金にならないカサ
Fishy, worthless leftovers.
琴線を奏でない言葉は無用
Words that don't pull at heartstrings are useless.
生活の 虜になっちゃったレイデー レイデー
I've become a captive of this life, Lady, Lady.
「痛かった」ってさえ 言えない秘密も
Even the secret of not being able to say "it hurt"...
そう生きていくため まともなものだもの
...is perfectly normal just to keep living.
他愛もないことでしょう
It's nothing special, is it?
レイデー レイデー
Lady, Lady.
あなたも虜でしょう
You're a captive too, aren't you?
うわああああ! ありがとう!
Waaaah! Thank you!
おめでとう!
Congratulations!
うるせー! ありがとう!
Shut up! Thank you!
え、え、来てくれてありがとう本当に。
E-e-, thank you so much for coming, really.
当たり前ですよ、来るじゃん。
Of course, I'd obviously come.
もう呼んでくれてありがとうね。
Thank you so much for inviting me.
ねえ、ありがとうね。もう嬉しい。
Right, thank you. I'm so happy.
やっぱ去年ね、なんか仲良くなった。めちゃくちゃ遊んだね、去年。
After all, we got close last year. We hung out a lot.
去年、あの嘘でね。
Last year, with that 'lie' game.
というね、あのゲームにね。めちゃめちゃ遊ばせてもらいました。
That game, right. We got to play it so much.
ありがとうございます。いやね、もう、ここに呼んだ理由も、やっぱ...
Thank you. Well, the reason I invited you here is...
声が曲に合うと思ったから。
...because I thought your voice would suit the song.
嬉しい!
I'm so happy!
やったぜ。え、めっちゃ練習しましたよ。
Alright. I practiced so much.
ありがとう。めっちゃいい声でした。
Thank you. Your voice was amazing.
本当? ありがとう。めっちゃいい声でした、もう。
Really? Thanks. It was a really good voice, really.
小さなアーニャ。
Little Anya.
いや、そんな変わらんって。結構変わってる? そんな変わらんって、もう。
Hey, it's not that different. Is it really? Not that different, really.
やっぱこのさ、後ろに飛んでるドローン。ずっと気になってて。
That drone flying behind us... I've been curious about it.
やっぱドローン気になるんだ。カメラになってるんだよね、実は。
So you are curious about it. It's actually a camera.
すごいよね、これね。こんな飛んでる。
It's amazing, isn't it. It's just flying there.
色々いいアングルも見せられたんじゃないかな。
I think we were able to show some good angles with it.
本当に素晴らしい、素敵な感じになったんじゃないでしょうか。
It really created a wonderful, lovely atmosphere.
ですね。うん、こちらのアーニャお披露目、まだまだ続いていくと。
Right. Yeah, this Anya showcase is still going on.
いや、本当に、呼んでもらって嬉しかったんで。また一緒に遊ぼう。
No, really, I'm glad you invited me. Let's hang out again.
ありがとう来てくれて。いつでも行くよ。また。
Thanks for coming. I'll come anytime. Later.
また遊ぼうね。ルーナも挟んで、3人でも。
Let's hang out again. With Luna too, the three of us.
絆、あるかどうかわかんないんですけど。あるよ、全然ある!
I don't know if we have 'bonds'... We do, definitely!
ねえ、次もルーナ先輩と遊びましょう。遊びましょう、3人で。
Right, let's hang out with Luna-senpai next time. Let's do it.
そねーちゃん、続きも頑張ってね。
Sone-chan, good luck with the rest.
ということで、僕はここでドロンです。ドロンだけに。
So, I'm gonna 'doron' (leave) here. Since it's a drone.
やばいだろ。ありがとう。バイバーイ!
That's terrible. Thank you. Bye-bye!
段々言葉を吐いた
Little by little, I spat out words.
あんな想い出に泣いたのは
Crying over those memories...
今日で終わりにするのか
...will you end it today?
1, 2の合図を待って
Waiting for the signal: 1, 2.
You & Me 手を取り合ったのは
You & Me, taking each other's hands...
僕の勇気ある行動
...was my courageous act.
お気に召すまま
At Your Pleasure
なら　エンドロールまで
So, until the end roll
そぞろなしいな　この人生
This life is a bit restless
退屈なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's boring, okay?
言わないでね
Don't say it, okay?
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now, okay?
僕ら今　さあさあ輪になって
We're now, come on, in a circle
回り始める　段々嫌になって
Beginning to spin, gradually getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
自分勝手も　ドンドン宙に舞って
Selfishness too, keeps dancing in the air
でも離れてく　パッパ音に乗って
But it drifts away, riding the sound
踊り始める　段々嫌になって
Beginning to dance, gradually getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
この先ずっと　僕の心をシェイクシェイクイェイ
From now on, forever, shake shake my heart, yeah
大正解なんてないのさ　じゃあ一体どこに向かえば
There's no right answer, so where should I head?
物語は終わりますか
Will the story end?
ワンツーの合図を待って　ユーアンドミー手が触れ合ったのは
Waiting for the one-two signal, you and me, our hands touched
僕の勇気ある行動
Because of my courageous action
フェイズ
Phase
畏まってたって　意味ないんだって
Being stiff is meaningless
恥ずかしがってた　夢にバイバイです
Goodbye to the dreams I was shy about
この先ずっと　よろしくね
From now on, forever, nice to meet you
君といま　さあさあ混ざり合って
With you now, come on, mixing together
目を逸らしあう　段々嫌になって
Avoiding each other's eyes, gradually getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
自分勝手も　トントン様になって
Selfishness too, starts to look good
崩れ落ちてく　パッパ触れる前に
Collapsing, before it can even touch
消えてしまうの　燦々嫌になって
Disappearing, completely getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
この先ずっと　分かり合えるまで僕たちは
From now on, forever, until we understand each other, we...
今更なんて言わないでね
Don't say it's too late now, okay?
僕ら今　さあさあ輪になって
We're now, come on, in a circle
回り始める　段々嫌になって
Beginning to spin, gradually getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
自分勝手も　ドンドン宙に舞って
Selfishness too, keeps dancing in the air
でも離れてく　パッパ音に乗って
But it drifts away, riding the sound
踊り始める　段々嫌になって
Beginning to dance, gradually getting sick of it
でも気になるね
But I'm still curious, aren't I?
目は離せないや
I can't take my eyes off it
この先ずっと　僕の心をシェイクシェイクイェイ
From now on, forever, shake shake my heart, yeah
わああ！　イェーイ！
Waaaa! Yay!
アーニャちゃん、3Dおめでとう！
Anya-chan, congrats on your 3D!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
来てくれてありがとう、わためぇ！
Thank you for coming, Watame!
いえいえ、呼んでくれてありがと！
No problem, thanks for inviting me!
やったぜ！
We did it!
やった、もう最高に楽しかったですね。
We did it, that was super fun.
そうだね。ロックだったね。
Right. It was rock.
ね、ロック。めちゃくちゃ、もう、体がね、止まらないの。
Yeah, rock. My body just... wouldn't stop.
ああ、これ、これずっとやってるもん。
Ah, I've been doing this the whole time.
アーニャが……アーニャの手が止まらねぇ！
Anya's... Anya's hand won't stop!
やめろ！　あああ！
Stop it! Aaaa!
やめろ！　俺のパンチやめて！
Stop it! Stop my punches!
ということでね、なんでこの曲選んだの？
So, why did you choose this song?
え、だって、わためちゃんにかっこいい曲、似合うからね。
Well, because cool songs suit you, Watame-chan.
嬉しい。え、大丈夫だった？　こんなやりたい放題させてもらって。
I'm happy. Uh, was it okay? Letting me run wild like this.
いやいやいや、これしかないやろ。
No no no, it had to be this.
これしかないよな、もう。
It had to be this, really.
これしかないよな。
It had to be this.
まあ、ロックしていこうぜ、この後も。
Well, let's keep rocking after this too.
ロックしていこうぜ！
Let's keep rocking!
ねー！　イェーイ！
Right! Yay!
もうね、あの、私達もね、気づいたんだけど……
You know, we also noticed that...
お、気づいたことがありました？
Oh, you noticed something?
なんと。顔が似てるんだよな！
Actually, our faces look similar!
お、似てる？　でかいということか？
Oh, similar? You mean they're big?
似てるよね、ほら見て。
They're similar, right? Look.
ほらほら、似てるよね。
Look, look, they're similar, right?
いや似てるって。瞳の色もね、同じだし。紫だしね。
I'm telling you, they're similar. Our eye color is the same too, both purple.
ね、顔でかいし。
And we have big faces.
やっぱり顔でけー！
Our faces are big after all!
...でかいでしょ
...is big, right?
もう どっちがでかいのか もうわかんないよ
I don't even know which one of us is bigger anymore.
まあね
Well, yeah.
ありがとね もう 来てくれて嬉しい
Thank you. I'm so happy you came.
こちらこそ こちらこそだよ
The pleasure is mine, really.
また遊ぼうね
Let's play again.
また遊ぼう
また遊びましょう わためぇ
Let's play again, Watame.
これも これもぜひ あの やりたいよね いつか
I'd definitely love to do this again sometime.
やりたい
I want to.
こういうゲーム あるよね
There are games like this, right?
こういうゲーム あるんじゃない
I think there are games like this.
あるんじゃない ねえ
There are, aren't there?
やろう やろうよ
Let's do it.
いつでも呼んで
Call me anytime.
ということで 来てくれてありがとう
So, thank you for coming.
お邪魔しました
Thank you for having me.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
Woi, kita akhirnya 3D!
Hey, we're finally 3D!
3D! Apa ya Allah!
3D! Oh my God!
Akhirnya 3D! Apa ya Allah!
Finally 3D! Oh my God!
Real banget! Wah real!
So real! Whoa, real!
Oh ya, di belakang itu apa? Apa itu?
Oh right, what's that behind us? What is it?
Oh my God! Kayaknya kalau kalian ngasih suportif komen
Oh my God! I think if you guys give supportive comments
dan superchat kayaknya bakal lebih berkilau deh.
and superchats, it'll be even shinier.
Oh my God! If you guys give supportive comments and Super Chats, it's gonna be even more SHINY!
Eh, by the way, kalian tahu kan ini lagu apa?
Eh, by the way, you guys know what song this is?
Ini kan... ini kan...
This is... this is...
Coba-coba suruh tebak, tebak, tebak.
Try asking them to guess, guess, guess.
Lagu apa dulu Chat? Ayo ayo.
What song is it first, Chat? Come on.
Tebak, tebak, tebak. Ayo ayo tebak.
Guess, guess, guess. Come on, guess.
Ada TV! Ada TV!
There's a TV! There's a TV!
Kureiji Ollie, bagaimana tadi? Kita... joget dan nyanyi...
Kureiji Ollie, how was that? We... danced and sang...
enggak nyanyi sih, joget tapi ke Identity Voices.
well not sang, but danced to Identity Voices.
How was that?
Gue baru tahu lu bisa nge-DJ!
I just found out you could DJ!
Iya, that's one of my hidden skills.
Yeah, that's one of my hidden skills.
Well, I've been living for like hundreds of years.
Oh benar juga, sudah lama.
Oh right, it's been a long time.
Makanya I have a lot of hidden skills. Dan Pavolia Reine, bagaimana tadi?
That's why I have a lot of hidden skills. And Pavolia Reine, how was that?
Tadi... kita ngapain aja ya? Saking hype-nya...
Just now... what were we doing? We were so hyped...
Saking hype-nya lupa kita ngapain aja.
So hyped I forgot what we did.
Kita nge-DJ dan joget... bergerak sendiri.
We were DJing and dancing... moving on our own.
Iya, bergerak. Bergerak. Aduh gila, seru banget gila.
Yeah, moving. Moving. Man, it was crazy fun.
Ya sudah berarti... ini aja enggak sih? Eh, by the way, itu udah berkilau!
Alright then... should we just do this? Eh, by the way, it's already shiny!
Ha? Enggak lah, tunggu, belum kita masih ada lagi!
Huh? No way, wait, we're not done yet!
Masih ada? Iya.
There's more? Yes.
Wah, apa tuh? Kita mau ngapain, Guys?
Whoa, what is it? What are we gonna do, guys?
Ngapain sih kira-kira?
What do you think?
Kita bakal... kita bakal itu enggak sih? Ini udah di stage bertiga.
We're gonna... we're gonna do that, right? We're already on stage together.
Kita mau nyanyi dan joget bareng!
We're gonna sing and dance together!
Yes! Kita atur-atur formasi dulu nanti.
Yes! Let's get into formation.
Oke, siap formasi nanti. Oke.
Okay, get ready for formation. Okay.
Oke, dengarkan, listen to our song...
Okay, listen, listen to our song...
our cover song I guess.
Oke! Gekkou!
Okay! Moonlight!
ガラクタだとかゴミを詰めて
Filled with junk and trash
ボロ布ひとつを被せた
I covered it with a rag
目に食い込んだ影をした
I had shadows digging into my eyes
偽物
Fake
誰かが紡いだ言葉を
Words someone else spun
誰かが奏でた色を
Colors someone else played
歪にコラージュした
I collaged them distortedly
偽物
Fake
一番最初の青の中
In the very first blue
革新的な少年の愛情が
A revolutionary boy's love
ほら
Look
僕ら気づいたらもう見えなくなる
By the time we noticed, we could no longer see
おもちゃ失くした子供も泣いている
Even the child who lost their toy is crying
どうしたら終わるのスポットライトに
When will it end? Under the spotlight
照らされている
Being illuminated
その背中は
That back
まだこの手から遠ざかっていく
Is still drifting further from this hand
あなたみたいになれやしなくて
I can never become like you
I can't become like you
あの月を追いかけるように
Like chasing that moon
渇いた心は
My parched heart
満たされないまま
Remains unfulfilled
ひとりになって、ひとりになって
All alone, all alone
くすんだ夢を見続けてしまった
I kept on seeing a faded dream
ガラクタだって、ボロギレだって
Even if it's junk, even if it's rags
その心臓が脈打つ限りには
As long as that heart beats
僕だけの怒りがあった
There was an anger only I could feel
足りないのは何だったんだろう
What was it that was missing?
神様に聞いてきたあとで
After I went to ask God
堕天使の弓矢に口止めされた
A fallen angel's arrow silenced me
初めから知っていたんだよ
I knew it from the start
忘れた芝居をしてんだよ
I'm just pretending I forgot
もらいもんの剣を抱きしめている
Clutching onto a borrowed sword
何十回目の失望だろう
How many times have I been disappointed now?
いっそ何もかも捨ててしまいたいと
I'd rather just throw everything away
結局最後は何にも残らない
In the end, nothing remains
愛も紡いでも名前も朽ちていく
Love and the names we weave also decay
どうしてだろう
I wonder why
この胸の奥にこびりついている
It's stuck deep within my chest
冬の夜の静寂に似た孤独を
A loneliness like the silence of a winter night
あなたはきっと知りもしないで
You surely won't even know
ひとりに星を見ていた
As you watched the stars alone
赤い目の僕に気も留めないまま
Without even noticing my red eyes
隣に立ってたあなた遠くで
You were standing right beside me, yet so far
くすんだ夢も見えなくなってしまって
Even the faded dream became invisible
それでも追い続けて
But I'll keep on chasing it anyway
偽物だって本当だって
Whether it's fake or real
振り返れば最後そこには
ぼやけた記憶があった
If I look back, in the end,
there's only a blurred memory
骸を貸したいのに
I want to lend my remains
クリシェを抜け出したいのに
I want to escape the cliché
また誰かの焼き直し？
Is this another rehash of someone else?
数多の星の屑たち
Multitudes of stardust
沈みゆくユーティリティ
A sinking utility
無慈悲な月の光
The merciless moonlight
アイデンティティさえまやかし？
Is even identity just a deception?
盗んででも愛が欲しい？
Do you want love even if you have to steal it?
何時の世も同じことばかり繰り返す
Repeating the same thing in every era
懐かしい歌が風に揺れている
A nostalgic song sways in the wind
あなたの声で教えてもらった言葉
The words I was taught by your voice
今でも忘れぬように
So that I won't forget them even now
書き留めている同じことを
I'm writing down the same things
あなたみたいになれやしなくて
I can't become like you
あの月を追いかけるように
Like chasing that moon
渇いた心は満たされないまま
My parched heart remains unfulfilled
時間が経って時間が経って
As time passes, as time passes
振り返る時目をそらさぬように
So I won't look away when looking back
なぞる僕たちは
We who trace our path
偽物だってボロギレだって
Whether we're fakes or rags
覚めた夢を抱いた先には
At the end of clutching a dream I woke from
僕だけの光がずっと
My own light will always remain
あ、OK guys, gimana tadi?
Ah, OK guys, how was that?
Emm, kita Holoro nyanyi bareng ya,
Umm, we Holoro sang together,
dan nge-DJ bareng.
and DJ'd together.
Oh my god, oh my god, capek. Capek.
Oh my god, oh my god, I'm tired. So tired.
OK, we sang Gekkou,
me, Ollie, and Reine sang Gekkou.
How was it?
It's one of my favorite songs and I'm so
happy I got to sing it with them!
And oh my god, ま、色々ありましたね。
And oh my god, well, lots of things happened.
かなた先輩とね、あの一緒にドロンしたし、
I 'disappeared' together with Kanata-senpai,
ま、私はドロンしてなかったんですけど。
well, I didn't actually disappear myself though.
で、わためちゃんともね、あのベースもね、
And with Watame-chan, the bass part too,
こう何にもね、あの弾きましたね。
we played it like this.
いやぁ、楽しかった！
Man, that was fun!
で、ID 2期生と一緒にDJ、そして「月光」歌いましたと。
And then the DJ session and singing
'Gekkou' with ID Gen 2.
いかがでしたでしょうか？ How was it everyone?
How was it? How was it everyone?
ま、このあともね、色々まだあるので。
Well, there's still more to come after this.
After this there's still some stuff
that I want to show you guys.
Oh my goodness.
あれ？あれ？
Huh? What?
ん？
Hmm?
What's that?
Wait what? What's that sound?
Hello? Wait what? What is that?
Something is flying. Wait what?
Ha, kaya terlihat familiar guys.
Ha, that looks familiar guys.
あれ？あれ知ってる顔だぞ。え？
Huh? I know that face. What?
ちょっと、ちょっと見てみたい。
Wait, I want to take a look.
あれちょっと近く、近くから見てみたい。あれ？
I want to see it from a bit closer. Huh?
Is that, wait, is that YAGOO?
Is that YAGOO? あれ？
Is that YAGOO? Huh?
Ha, YAGOO ke sini guys.
Ha, YAGOO's coming here guys.
YAGOO-nya, YAGOO-nya bisa melayang dong kocak.
YAGOO, YAGOO can fly! That's hilarious.
YAGOO beneran woi.
It's really YAGOO.
Hai, YAGOO, YAGOO-nya bisa melayang.
Hi, YAGOO, YAGOO can fly.
YAGOO！
YAGOO!
YAGOOさん、こっちこっち！
YAGOO-san, over here, over here!
あれ？一体何が？
Huh? What on earth?
あれ？
Wait...
YAGOOさんですよね？
You're Yagoo-san, right?
飛べるんですか？
Can you fly?
そうですね。
That's right.
アーニャさん、3Dお披露目おめでとうございます。
Anya-san, congratulations on your 3D debut.
ええ、もしかして...
Wait, could it be...
...今日わざわざここまで？
...you came all the way here today?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
せっかくなので、
Since we have this opportunity,
まあ我々ホロライブID2期生はね、
well, we, Hololive ID Gen 2,
3Dお披露目をしたわけなんですけれども、
have just had our 3D debuts,
YAGOOさんのご感想を聞きたいんですが、
but I'd like to hear Yagoo-san's thoughts,
いただいてもよろしいですか？
if that's alright?
ホロライブインドネシアの皆さんも、
Everyone in Hololive Indonesia,
1期生に続いて2期生の皆さんも
after Gen 1, now Gen 2 as well,
3Dお披露目できて、とても良かったと思います。
I think it's wonderful that you could all debut in 3D.
おお、はい、ありがとうございます。
Oh, yes, thank you very much.
あれ、大丈夫かなこれYouTube的に。
Wait, is this okay for YouTube?
大丈夫かな。
I wonder if it's okay.
まあ、そうですね、ありがとうございます。
Well, anyway, thank you very much.
最後に、ええと、
Lastly, um,
今日の晩御飯何を食べてたか教えていただきたいです。
I'd like you to tell me what you had for dinner today.
今日は奥さんの手料理を食べました。
Today, I ate my wife's home cooking.
ほお、幸せそうですね声から。
Oh, you sound happy.
いや、ありがとうございました。
Well, thank you very much.
以上です。
That's all.
お帰り気をつけてください。
Please be careful on your way back.
バイバイ、YAGOO、YAGOOさん！
Bye-bye, Yagoo, Yagoo-san!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
YAGOOさんありがとう来てくれて。
Yagoo-san, thank you for coming.
Thank you!
Oh my god, I can't believe Yagoo actually visited.
Gila tadi Yagoo-san dateng.
Crazy, Yagoo-san came just now.
Gila banget gak sih guys?
Isn't that crazy, guys?
Anyways, I still have like some more things to show to you guys.
So let's go to the next stage!
じゃあ、次のステージに移動しようかな。
Well then, I guess I'll move to the next stage.
次はIDアリーナだ！
Next is ID Arena!
うわー！ギ（gila）ステージ（stage）APA（apa）NI（ni）！
Whoa! What kind of crazy stage is this!
うわ、IDアリーナのアーニャ・メルフィッサだ！
Whoa, it's Anya Melfissa's ID Arena!
ステージ（stage）SIAPA（siapa）LAGI（lagi）？フゥ！
Whose stage else? Whoo!
Welcome to ID Arena Anya Melfissa version!
This is my, my ID arena stage.
And I will be singing a special song.
Aku di sini akan nyanyi ya guys.
I'm going to sing here, guys.
Nyanyi apa?
Sing what?
Well, my original song.
で、ここで何するかというと、えー1曲ね、歌います。
And what I'm going to do here is sing one song.
何の曲なのかね、あの私のあのオリジナル曲、
As for what song it is, well, my original song,
初のオリジナル曲。
my first original song.
My first original song.
Please listen to it.
Unreal Veil.
アンリアルヴェイル。
アンリアルヴェイル
Lyrics・Composition: ぼっちぼろまる
Arrangement: HAMA-kgn (Felion Sounds)
Unreal Veil
Lyrics・Composition: Bocchi Boromaru
Arrangement: HAMA-kgn (Felion Sounds)
どっからどう見ても品行方正
However you look at me, I'm well-behaved
いたって真面目でいいじゃんね
I'm perfectly serious, and that's fine, right?
眼鏡かけ歩く天真爛漫
Innocently walking around with my glasses on
本当の自分がわからない
I don't know who my true self is
マスクを付けて隠してる
Wearing a mask to hide away
泣きそうな顔全部隠してる
Hiding every part of my tearful face
夜がくるたびに思い出してる
Recalling it every time night falls
空駆けシュレッダー隠してく
Hiding the shredder that races across the sky
もう　うんざりかい？
Are you fed up already?
アンリアルなままで絶好調で
In top form while remaining unreal
隠してた本当の自分も
Even the true self I kept hidden
有耶無耶にならないで
Don't let it become vague
甘い嘘も本当にしよう
Let's turn even sweet lies into truth
可愛く笑って
Smile cutely
楽しく笑って
Smile happily
君が笑っている
You are smiling
アンリアルヴェイル
Unreal Veil
コードの上を伝っていくんだ
Transmitting over the cords
ひとつの迷いも揺らさずに
Without letting a single doubt waver
夜が来たならば公明正大
When night comes, it's fair and square
嫌いなものは捨てちまえ
Throw away everything you hate
オッケー
Okay
さあ信じてんじゃん？
Now, aren't you believing?
気にする奴は知らんね
I don't care about those who mind
へなちょこなのなんて気にすんな
Don't worry about being a weakling
一瞬で離せよ走り出した世界に
Let go in an instant to the world that's started running
自分で決める神様
The god who decides for themselves
案外弱いみたいな心象
An unexpectedly weak impression
全部さらけ出してしまいな
Just lay it all bare
散々悩んだって
No matter how much you worry
独りきりじゃ歩けないよ
You can't walk all alone
Say Ho!
悪いことしたら神様が見てる
If you do something bad, God is watching
なんて嘘なんじゃないなんて聞かない
I won't ask if that's a lie
神すら見せないFAKE FAKE
A FAKE FAKE that not even God can see
信じてないだなんて誰も言ってない
No one said they don't believe
散々揺れるマスクをとって
Taking off the heavily swaying mask...
綺麗な自分を晒すんだ
Exposing my beautiful self
全然生きてるじゃんね
I'm totally alive, right?
怖い？辛い？鼻をくくろう
Afraid? Hurting? Let's turn our noses up
今日からまた叫んじょうぜ
From today, let's scream again
隠してた本当の自分を
The true self you've been hiding
ある観客になんないで
Don't just be an observer
甘い？歌も本当にしよう
Naive? Let's make even the song real
可愛く笑って
Smile cutely
楽しく舞って
Dance joyfully
君が笑っているリアルな今日
A real today where you are smiling
戦うんだ嘘も吐いて
I'll fight, even telling lies
それもいつかは本当さ 絵も伝う
Even that will be the truth someday, words also flow
アンリアルヴェイル
Unreal Veil
Whoa! How was that?
My first original song!
Bagaimana guys? Original song pertamaku.
How was it, guys? My first original song.
Bagi yang sering nanyain, "Ori song mana Anya? Ori song mana Anya?"
For those who often ask, "Where's the original song, Anya? Where's the original song, Anya?"
Tuh, dedek! Gimana? Gimana? Keren banget kan?
There it is! How was it? How was it? It was so cool, right?
And oh my god, do you guys know that that same original song will be digitally releasing? Here's the jacket!
「アンリアルヴェイル」作曲ぼっちぼろまるさんの「アンリアルヴェイル」、私の初のオリ曲でございます。デジタルリリース決定！
"Unreal Veil" composed by Bocchi Boromaru-san, my first original song. Digital release confirmed!
It will be digitally releasing at July 29th at 0 AM, your time zone.
デジタルリリースなんですけど、夜中のね、あの0時。29日夜中の0時ね、あの決定いたしました。
As for the digital release, it's at midnight, 0 AM. It's set for July 29th at midnight.
さらに！Not only that, but also my second original song will be digitally releasing as well!
Furthermore! Not only that, but also my second original song will be digitally releasing as well!
Not only one song, but two! Two songs!
さらに、あの第二のオリジナル曲も同じ時間でデジタルリリース決定！
Furthermore, the digital release of my second original song at the same time is confirmed!
作曲ゆのすけさんです。作曲ゆのすけさんの「Everlasting knife」！
Composed by Yunosuke-san. "Everlasting knife" by Yunosuke-san!
Not only one original songs, but two! Oh my goodness, spicy!
And also, it's not ending yet. I have a special teaser for you guys.
And what is it? What teaser is it? It's for my Unreal Veil MV! Here it is.
Digital Release : 2023.7.29 00:00 (土)
MV Release : 2023.8.03 21:00 (木)
Digital Release : 2023.7.29 00:00 (Sat)
MV Release : 2023.8.03 21:00 (Thu)
Oh my god, are you winning Mel-friends? Oh my goodness!
My original song MV will be premiering at August 3rd.
オリ曲のMVはですね、なんと8月3日プレミア公開決定でございます！
As for the original song MV, it will have a premiere release on August 3rd!
Please wait for more infos about it. Hehe!
And also, one more announcement. What is it? Here it is!
Wah! Ada goods lucu banget lho!
Whoa! There's some really cute merch!
さらに、えっとちょっと待ってくださいね。なんとですね...
Furthermore, uh, please wait a moment. You see...
なんとですね、実物も今持っています！
Believe it or not, I have the actual item right here!
This cushion! So cute!
It will be on sale tomorrow after the Holoro mini-live, by the way.
明日のあのID二世のミニライブ後でね、あの発売でございます！
It will be on sale after tomorrow's ID 2nd generation mini-live!
Anya Melfissa's special cushion! So cute!
Ya,楽しみだね！
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it!
And also, don't forget everyone, tomorrow, Holoro mini-live!
Ada Holoro mini-live ya besok guys, jangan lupa!
There's a Holoro mini-live tomorrow, guys, don't forget!
And yeah, that's it! Oh my god, thank you so much.
Thank you so much everyone for supporting till the end. Thank you, thank you!
いや、こんな感じの3Dお披露目でございます。
Well, this was my 3D showcase.
いや、本当にみんな、ありがとう！Thank you so much everyone!
Man, truly everyone, thank you! Thank you so much everyone!
And I'll see you guys tomorrow with Ollie and Reine!
明日のね、あのミニライブもよろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to tomorrow's mini-live as well!
いや、感動するね。感動しますね。
Man, I'm moved. It's moving.
Oh my god. I'm filled with a lot of feelings.
No, oh my god.
Well but that's it.
That's it
for me,
I will be signing out.
See you guys tomorrow.
And... Otsukris!
Otsukris semuanya,
Otsukris everyone,
Otsukris everyone!
皆さん、おつくリスです！
Everyone, Otsukris!
Bye bye, Otsukris!
THANK YOU.
THIS WILL BE AN UNFORGETTABLE DAY OF MY ANCIENT WEAPON LIFE.
PLEASE KEEP ON SUPPORTING ME
3D SHOWCASE